Guide to the Lawrence A. Brown Papers, 1963-2004 RG.40.351
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Accession Number UA.2014.0228, 1963-2004; 6.0 Cubic feet; (5) cartons
  - The Diffusion of a Population-Related Innovation: The Planned Parenthood Affiliate. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 13)
  - Infrastructure Growth and Adoption: The Diffusion of Cable Television within a Community. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 14)
  - The Diffusion of Community Innovations: A Conceptualization and Empirical Analysis. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 15)
  - Adopter Categories in a Spatial Context Revisited: Alternative Explanations for an Empirical Regularity. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 16)
  - The Provision of Innovations within the Context of Geographical Diffusion Theory. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 17)
  - Diffusion Agency Strategy and the Adoption of Infrastructure Independent Innovations: A Case Study of the Eastern Ohio Resource Development Center. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 18)
  - The Adoption of Credit Card Services by Banks: A Case Study of Innovation Diffusion in a Polynuclear Setting with Central Propagator Support. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 19)
  - Diffusion Waves within the Context of Regional Economic Development. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 20)
  - Propagator Supported Diffusion Processes: Agency Strategies and the Innovation Establishment Interface. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 21)
  - Innovation Diffusion in a Developing Economy: A Meso-Scale View. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 22)
  - An experimental Approach to the Study of Diffusion Agency Establishment Processes. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 23)
  - Annotated Bibliography of Geographic Diffusion Studies. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 24)
  - Acquaintance Circles and Communication: An Exploration of Hypotheses Relating to Innovative Adoption. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 25)
  - Simmar: A Markov Chain Based Program for the Diffusion of Innovation. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 26)
  - Adopter Categories in a Spatial Context: Artificial Insemination in Southern Sweden. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 27)
  - The Diffusion of Cable Television in Ohio: A Case Study of Diffusion Agency Location Patterns and Processes of the Polynuclear Type. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 28)
  - Diffusion in a Growth Pole Context: A Comment. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 29)
  - Cones of Resolution in Spatial Diffusion Studies: A Perspective. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 30)
  - The Market and Infrastructure Context of Adoption: a Perspective on the Spatial Diffusion of Innovation. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 31)
  - The Diffusion of Innovation: a Markov Chain-Type Approach. Northwestern University Geography Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 32)
  - Models for Spatial Diffusion Research: A Review. ONR Project report, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 33)
  - GAC: a Computer Program for Analysis of Linear Covariance. University of Iowa Geography Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 34)
  - Diffusion Research in Geography: A Perspective. University of Iowa Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 35)
  - Transmap: a Program for Planar Transformation of Point Distributions. Ohio State University Geography Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 36)
  - Population and Migration in an Urban context: a Spatial Perspective. Ohio State University Geography Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 37)
  - Centro: A Program for Centrographic Measures. Ohio State University Geography Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 38)
  - Day Care Centers in Columbus: A Locational Strategy. Ohio State University Geography Discussion Paper Series, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 39)
  - NSF Institutes, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 40)
  - Choice Mechanisms in the Migration Decision. Ford Foundation Project Report, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 41)
  - Book Reviews, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 42)
  - Rutledge- Materials/Reviews, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 43)
  - Reviews, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 44)
  - Innovation Diffusion Book, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 45)
  - Studies in Innovation Diffusion Processes, 2: Conceptual Considerations, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 46)
  - "Urban System Evaluation at the Ecuador Amazon Frontier" Geographical Review, 2000 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 1)
  - "The GIS/SA Interface for Substantive Research(ers): A Critical Need" Journal of Geographical Systems, 2000 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 2)
  - "Change, Community and the Pursuit of Geographic understanding, Presidential Address" Annals of the Association of American Geographers, 1999 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 3)
  - "Urban Development at the Ecuador Amazon Frontier: Boom Towns or Gloom Towns?" Developing Frontier Cities: Global Perspectives, 1999 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 4)
  - Economic Restructuring and Migration in an Old Industrial Region: the Ohio River Valley, 1999 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 5)
  - "Towards a GeoEd Research Agenda: Observations of Concerned Bystander" Professional Geography, 1999 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 6)
  - "Gender, Migration and the Organization of Work Under Economic Devolution; Ecuador 1982-90" International Journal of Population Geographer, 1998 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 7)
  - "Development Models, Economic Adjustment, and Occupational Composition: Ecuador 1982-90" International Regional Science Review, 1997 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 8)
  - "Regional Change as the Interplay of Global and Local", 1997 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 9)
  - "Continuity and Change in an Old Industrial Region: the Ohio River Valley", 1982-1990 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 10)
  - Urban System Evolution in Frontier Settings. Geographic Review, 1994 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 11)
  - Frontier Migration, Multistage phenomenon. Papers in Regional Science, 1994 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 12)
  - Complement Perspective Means of Understanding. Regional Change: Frontier Settlements in Ecuador, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 13)
  - Causes of Tropical Deforestation in Ecuador, 1992 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 14)
  - Innovation diffusion: Retrospect and Prospect, 1990 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 15)
  - Location, Soc Category, Individual Labor Market: Venezuela, 1989 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 16)
  - Migrant Fertility Differentials, Ecuador, 1989 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 17)
  - Polar Reverse, Migration Shifts, Human Resource Profile: Venezuela, 1989 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 18)
  - Policy Aspect Development, Individual Mobility: Mig-Circ, Ecuador Rural Sierra, 1988 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 19)
  - Reflections, Third world Development, 1988 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 20)
  - Development Related Context Effects, Individual Attrib, Migration: Venezuela, 1987 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 21)
  - Migration, Human Resource Transfer, Development context: Logit Analy, Venezuela, 1987 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 22)
  - Struct Tension, Migration, Development: Venezuela, 1987 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 23)
  - Family Plan: Review, Concept Frame, 1986 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 24)
  - Rural-Non Farm Employment, Migration: Costa Rica, 1986 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 25)
  - Circ-Migration: Comparison In Ecuador, 1985 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 26)
  - Cross national tests 3rd World Development-Migration paradigm, Venezuela, 1985 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 27)
  - Migration, Uneven Development, conventional Modeling: Costa Rica, 1985 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 28)
  - Rural Dest. Migration in 3rd World Setg. Regional Studies, 1985 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 29)
  - Spatial Variation in Migration, Development: Costa Rica. Demography, 1985 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 30)
  - Innovation Diffusion, Entrepreneurial Activity. Research in Marketing, Vol.4, 1981 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 31)
  - Place Utility, Attribution Trade Off, Choice Behavior, Intra-Urban Migration, 1981 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 32)
  - Market Penetration, Location Conflict in Franchise Systems. Decision Sciences, 1980 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 33)
  - Diff. Agency Establishment: Friendly Ice Cream, 1979 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 34)
  - Innovation Diffusion: Cooperative Movement in Sierra Leone, 1979 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 35)
  - The Community Innovation Process, 1978 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 36)
  - Spatial Diff. of Innovation: Gaming Approach, 1978 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 37)
  - Landscape Evolution, Diffusion Processes, 1977 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 38)
  - Promar: The New Product Marketing Game. Computer Applications, 1977 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 39)
  - Diff. of Planned Parenthood Affiliation., 1977 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 40)
  - Place Attributes in Migration., 1977 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 41)
  - Strateg., Promo-Diff. of Consumer Goods-Services., 1977 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 42)
  - Acquaint Circles, Communication, Innovation Adoption., 1976 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 43)
  - Adopter Category in Spatial Context: Altern. Explan. Empiric Region., 1976 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 44)
  - Cones of Resolution in Spatial Diffusion Studies, 1976 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 45)
  - Diffusion Waves, Regional Economic Development. Journal of Regional Science, 1976 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 46)
  - Simmar: Markov Chain Prog., Innovation Diffusion. Computer Applications, 1976 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 47)
  - Mkt-Infrastructure Context of Adoption, 1975 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 48)
  - Cable Television in Ohio: Diffusion Agency Polynuclear Type, 1974 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 49)
  - Location of Urban Pop Service Facilities: Day Care Centers, 1974 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 50)
  - Innovation Diffusion in Developing Economy: Meso-Scale View, 1973 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 51)
  - Behavioral Approaches in Geography, 1972 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 52)
  - Diffusion Through an Urban System, 1972 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 53)
  - Facil. Location Under Max Travel Restrict: Day Care Facilities, 1972 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 54)
  - Centro: Program for Centrograph Measures., 1971 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 55)
  - Delimit Function Regions, Nodal Regions, Hier: Function Diffusion Approach, 1971 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 56)
  - Empiric Region in Diffusion of Innovation, 1971 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 57)
  - Intra-Urban Migration Lifelines: Spatial View. Demography, 1971 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 58)
  - Search Behavior, Intra-Urban Migration Context, 1971 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 59)
  - Functional Dist.: Operational Approach. Geographic Analysis, 1970 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 60)
  - Intra-Urban Migration Process: Perspective, 1970 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 61)
  - Migration Flows in Intra-Urban Space: Place Utility. Annals of AAG, 1970 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 62)
  - Migration, Functional dist., Urban Hierarchy., 1970 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 63)
  - Place Utility and Normative Alloc of Intra-Urban Migrants, 1970 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 64)
  - Social Area Change: Empiric Analysis. Urban Studies, 1970 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 65)
  - Urban Acquaintance Fields. Environment and Planning A, 1970 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 66)
  - Use of Markov Chains, Movement Research. Economic Geography, 1970 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 67)
  - Diffusion of Innovation: Macroview., 1969 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 68)
  - Diff Research in Geography: Perspective. Progress in Geography 1, 1969 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 69)
  - Transmap: Program, Planar Transform point Distributions. Discussion Paper 3 OSU, 1969 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 70)
  - Search, Learn, Marketing Decision Process., 1967 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 71)
  - A Simulation Model of Migration and Development. In Modeling and Simulation Volume 13, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 72)
  - On the Interrelationships between development and migration processes. Geographic Research on Latin America: Benchmark, 1980 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 73)
  - Continuity amidst restructuring: the U.S. Gender Division of Labor in Geographic Perspective. International Regional Science Review, 1970 and 1990 (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 74)
  - Racial/Ethnic residential sorting in spatial context: Testing the explanatory frameworks. Urban Geography, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 75)
  - The market and infrastructure perspective: A missing link in understanding the diffusion of broadband adoption in Oklahoma. The Annals of Regional Science, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 76)
  - Market led pluralism: Rethinking our understanding of racial/ethnic spatial patterning in U.S. cities., undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 77)
  - Population Growth. Geography in America, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0005, Folder 78)